

DANIEL DOMINGUEZ Software Product Manager

Project Manager / Certified ScrumMaster®

September 26, 1982 35 years old Colombian, Single



K 49 No 91-86 AP 402 Bogotá, COLOMBIA



(+57) 319-219-4399 (+57 1) 675-1189



dominguezdaniel @live.com



dominguezdaniel



dominguezdaniel



@dominguezdaniel



dominguezdaniel



http://x.co/idaniel

SUMMARY

Engineer with studies from Colombia, France and Canada. Over 8 years of experience working on Internet-related products and services companies in Colombia and USA. With major expertise on Agile Methodologies, Project Management, Product Development, Digital Marketing and Entrepreneurship.

EXPERIENCE

Product Owner, Webpy webpy.co

Colombia/USA — Jan 2017 - Oct 2017

Product planning, ideation and release under design thinking and lean methodologies.

Scrum Master, Torre Technologies torre.co

Colombia/USA — Dec 2014 - Dec 2016

Certified ScrumMaster®. Agile scrum development framework for managing product.

Project Manager, DLD Agencia Digital dld.com.co

Colombia/USA — Apr 2014 - Nov 2014

Planning and execution on Google engagement and web app implementations.

Project Manager, VML vml.com

Colombia/USA — Oct 2013 - Mar 2013

Planning, execution and closing projects for Boehringer Ingelheim, Merck and MediaFiche.

Online Marketing Manager, .CO Internet go.co

Colombia/USA — Aug 2012 - May 2013

Tracking and evaluation of marketing initiatives for .CO domains.

Co-Founder, I-Azul i-azul.com

Colombia/USA — Jan 2009 - Jul 2012

Consulting, strategy and development in E-Business, E-Commerce and E-Marketing.

EDUCATION

University of Alberta (Canada)

Specialization, Software Product Management — 2015-2016

Université Pierre et Marie Curie (France)

Master's Degree, Engineering Science — 2008-2008

Université des Sciences et Technologies de Lille (France)

Professional Master, Automation — 2006-2007

Universidad Militar Nueva Granada (Colombia)

Engineer, Mechatronics — 2000-2005

LANGUAGES

Spanish (Native), English (Full Proficiency), French (Full Proficiency)

SKILLS

HTML/CSS, GIT, VPL, SQL, Web Design, Agile/Scrum/Kanban, Project Management, Communication Skills, Online Marketing, Google Analytics/Adwords, Atlassian Suite.

INTERESTS

Robots, Arduino, Programming, Gig Economy, Reading, Traveling, Top Eleven, Zen.

REFERENCES

Omar Duque, Director of Engineering at Huge (+57) 300-386-7557 - Colombia **Lorena Dominguez**, Sister, UI/UX Specialist (+1) 437- 983-8050 - Canada